{
    "subject": "resource/GG_Allin",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Hardcore_punk",
    "human_readable": "The genre of GG Allin's work is Hardcore punk.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6137529015541077,
            "question": "What genre of music is GG Allin known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.611887514591217,
            "question": "Which music genre did GG Allin primarily perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5975139141082764,
            "question": "What is the name of the music genre associated with GG Allin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.536954402923584,
            "question": "How would you describe the musical genre that GG Allin represented?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4963482618331909,
            "question": "What kind of music did GG Allin perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49383091926574707,
            "question": "To what musical subgenre does GG Allin belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4901432693004608,
            "question": "In what musical category is GG Allin's work classified?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47322168946266174,
            "question": "What is GG Allin's musical style characterized by?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42049896717071533,
            "question": "What type of music made GG Allin famous?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4145536720752716,
            "question": "Describe the type of music GG Allin created."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The genre of GG Allin's work is Hardcore punk.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8508_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of music made GG Allin famous?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8508_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is GG Allin's musical style characterized by?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8508_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what musical category is GG Allin's work classified?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8508_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8508_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8508_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8508_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8508_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8508_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8508_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8508_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8508_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8508_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8508_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The genre of GG Allin's work is Hardcore punk.\" Specifically, they describe his notorious and confrontational performances typical of hardcore punk, as well as his impact on the punk rock scene."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}